Don't get on everything you see an
influencer tell you on TikTok is going
to help your longevity. Just say [music]
no. What works for a 20-something
influencer on TikTok might not be the
thing your 70-year-old uh mother or
friend should try.
>> [music]
>> The longevity industry, just the
therapeutic side of development, sitting
around 23 billion worldwide. And I think
it's projected to almost double within
the next 8 years. We're at this pivotal
moment where at a population level we
are living longer. So, it's not a matter
of science fiction. It's a matter of
what tools do we have in front of us
right now. [music] I'm not a what I
would call a big biohacker. I don't use
a lot of off-label drugs. Start with the
basics. If I'm not exercising, if I'm
not watching my diet, if I'm not doing
the very basic things of getting some
sunshine, engaging with those around me,
and sharing a little bit of love every
day, me thinking that I'm going to find
purpose and meaning in the next pill is
pretty unlikely. So, we can get so
caught up trying to perfect our health
and do the next thing for our longevity
that we forget to actually enjoy the
day.
>> [music]
>> Um and so I'd say if if anything is a
mantra, it's that.